The first scientific journal was published in 1665.
Before that, research results spread mostly through personal communication-
-and handwritten material.
To disseminate research results through scientific journals-
-Haves come to become an important part of the scientific system-
-And over the years, tens of thousands of scientific journals have been started.
Until digitalisation needed publishers and printing companies-
-For everything for packaging and dissemination of the magazines.
Researchers' need to spread and quality assure their results-
-eventually come to become a market.
In the 1960s, large stock marketed publishers began to buy up less-